ecreativeworks.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Industrial Website Design - Ecreativeworks, Inc.

7545 Irvine Center Drive, Suite 200  
Irvine, CA 926180  
ph: 949-629-1171 

13220 County Road 6, Suite 150  
Plymouth, MN 55441  
ph: 763-450-3900  

## Effective: July 1, 2004

Ecreativeworks is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website and will not sell or provide any non-public personal information to anyone without your permission. 

**Types of Information  
**  
Cookies. A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows us to identify your computer without requiring your disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve [replica handbags](http://www.cheapmulberryonsale.org/) information through your Internet browser. A Cookie itself cannot read information off a hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites.

General Information is information that does not itself reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type, SIC code, information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet), user behavior on our website, and aggregated generic information.

Non-Public Personal Information is any non-public information you provide to us or our Partners that is proprietary or identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information [replica mulberry handbags](http://www.cheapmulberryonsale.org/mulberry) may include, without limitation: name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, account information, voting behavior, spending patterns, and individual tastes and preferences.

Partners are individuals or entities we engage to help us carry out our mission.

**What Information We Collect**

Ecreativeworks collects general information and non-public personal information.

**How We Collect Our Information**

Ecreativeworks collects our general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of the website.

Non-public personal information is collected through registration or contact forms on this site and will never be used for any purpose other than internal [mulberry bags outlet](http://www.cheapmulberryonsale.org/mulberry) use or by our partners unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (this is a choice made by the registrant on the Registration form).

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Any changes to this privacy policy will be posted here and unless otherwise noted on our website.

**Changing your non-public personal information**

Ecreativeworks provides you with the opportunity to change your non-public personal information online for all registration information. Please contact Ecreativeworks to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form.

If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us at [privacy@ecreativeworks.com](mailto:privacy@ecreativeworks.com%20).

Interested? [Click here](http://www.ecreativeworks.com/contact.php) to request more information.
